So we have two DeepSeeks.
One is the DeepSeeks company,
which is Guangzhou,
DeepSeeks Artificial Intelligence,
Basic Technology Research Co.
Big name, you know.
It's a pretty long name.
It also has a LTD over here, limited.
But it's working as DeepSeeks, which is the company.
And the company DeepSeeks,
which is a private company,
as you see over here from China,
owns a product,
which is called DeepSeeks as well.
Like how Google owns Google, you know,
Google is the company,
which was renamed to Alphabet for a small time.
Whatever, Google is the company.
And we also have Google, which is the search engine, right?
So this is how DeepSeeks works.
There's a DeepSeeks, which is the company,
and a product, which is called DeepSeeks, the chatbot, right?